jainuniversity.ac.in 2019-03-01

# Privacy Policy of Jain (Deemed-to-be University) - Banagalore, India

#### **Privacy Policy Summary**

Thank you for reviewing our privacy policy and visiting the Jain (Deemed-to-be University) website / webpages. Our policy is quite simple - we never collect any personal information about any individual unless you choose to provide that information to us. We do not give, share, sell, or transfer any personal information to a third party or we won’t use them for marketing activities.

#### Cookies

We use "cookies" on certain Jain (Deemed-to-be University) webpages to help you use our websites interactively on a regular basis. A cookie is a small file that a website transfers to your computer's hard disk, usually to keep track of you while you are connected to that website.

The cookies on Jain (Deemed-to-be University) webpages do not collect any personal information about individuals, but only about your browser "session." The cookie makes it easier for you to use the dynamic features of these webpages, without providing the same information again as you move from one page to another.

In order to protect your privacy, be sure to close your browser completely after you have finished conducting business with a website that uses cookies. If you are much concerned about the potential use of information gathered from your computer by cookies, you can set your browser to prompt you before it accepts a cookie. Most Internet browsers have settings that let you identify and/or reject cookies.

#### Information from e-mail

If in case you decide to send us an electronic mail message (e-mail), it will usually contain your return e-mail address. If you include personally-identifying information in your e-mail because you want us to address issues specific to your situation, we may use that information in responding to your request. Also, e-mail is not necessarily secure against interception. Please send only information necessary to help us process your request.

#### Non-personal information will be recorded

If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the website, read pages, or download information, our website's operating system will automatically record some general information about your visit. 

During your visit, our web operating system will record:

  * 1\. The **Internet domain** for your internet service, such as "xyz.com" or "xyz.net" if you use a private internet access account, or "yourcollege.edu" if you connect from a college or university domain. 
  * 2\. The **type of browser** ("Google Chrome version X” or "Internet Explorer version X") that you are using.
  * 3\. The **type of operating system** that you use (Macintosh, UNIX, or Windows).
  * 4\. The **date and time** you visit our site, and the **web pages that you visit** on our site.
  * 5\. The address of the **previous website** you were visiting, if you linked to us from another website.

We use this information typically for growth analysis, to help us make our site more useful to visitors. This tracking system does not record information about individuals. 

### Information collected from interactive forms

On some of our webpages, we offer interactive forms that let you voluntarily submit personal information (such as your e-mail address, name, or organization). This occurs when you are registering for online counselling, various tests, quizzes, seminars, workshops, or training sessions offered by Jain (Deemed-to-be University), downloading admission forms from Jain (Deemed-to-be University). In those cases, all submitted information is used only for the purposes for which it is intended and is not made available to any third party.
